insideiim.com 2018-10-14

# Privacy Policy ⋆ InsideIIM.com

We at KiRa9 Edumedia Pvt. Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as KiRa9), are committed to protecting the privacy of our users, and strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. With respect to this Privacy Policy, the terms “User/s” shall be taken to mean any person accessing the KiRa9 Website/s, including but not limited to Readers, Students, Contributors, Authors, Job Seekers, Recruiters, Advertisers, etc.

This Privacy Policy sets forth the online data collection terms, usage policies and practices that apply to KiRa9 and its Websites. The following policy explains KiRa9 Edumedia Pvt Ltd.’s commitment to securely managing your personal information and sets out how and when personal information is collected, held, used or disclosed. This Privacy Policy only applies to data gathered by Kira9 either offline or online through various KiRa9 Websites (hereinafter referred to as the “Kira9 WebSite/s”) accessed through desktop or mobile platforms, however, it does not apply to data collected by any other company or website.

By registering or by using any KiRa9 WebSite, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use and transfer of the personal information provided by you in the manner described in this Policy. Please read this Policy carefully as it affects your rights and liabilities under law. If you do not accept the Privacy Policy stated herein or disagree with the way we collect and process personal information collected on the Kira9 WebSite/s, please refrain from accessing the same.

A] USER INFORMATION  
We, at KiRa9 Edumedia Pvt Ltd., are committed to respecting your privacy online and offline and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you share with us. “Personal Information” means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address, an email address, a telephone or mobile number or any other contact information, whether of work or home. In general, you can visit KiRa9’s WebSite/s without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. We collect information from you when you register on any our Kira9 WebSite/s, subscribe to receive our newsletter or posts or stories, subscribe to receive job or vacancies posted on Kira9 WebSite/s, upload your resume or voluntarily share your personal information with us, respond to a survey or fill out any form. We also collect information through our online and offline surveys, through events and seminars organized by us, or when you interact with any of our employees or Kira9 staff.

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy. You however agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze Kira9 WebSite/s usage, improve the Websites content and product/service offerings, and customize our WebSite/s content, layout, and services. Such use help us improve our WebSite/s and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Kira9 WebSite/s. You also agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Kira9 WebSite/s. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. [Optional]

B] USE OF INFORMATION  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve any of our Kira9 WebSite/s (we continually strive to improve our Website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To communicate with you respect to any essays/articles/stories/jobs/posts/videos that you may have chosen to submit on the Kira9 WebSite/s and to initiate communication between you and another user of the Kira9 WebSite/s (for example a Recruiter/Job Seeker/University).
  * To process payment transactions, if any.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To monitor the messenger service offered on our Kira9 WebSite/s
  * To send periodic emails – The email address you provide while registering, may be used to send you newsletters, information and updates pertaining to the Kira9 WebSite/s or matters that we think may interest you, in addition to sending occasional company news, updates, related product or services information, etc.

C] DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION  
The personal data shared by you on any of the Kira9 WebSite/s may be used by KiRa9 for their internal purposes. However, no personal information pertaining to you, including customary basic information such as name, city and email id, shall be provided to any Third Party without acquiring your express permission. The permission sought may be in the form of a checkbox which you can tick while creating your profile, or through an email or a call. The permission received through any of the above modes shall be considered as an express consent given by you towards sharing your information with any Third Party.

By accessing Kira9 WebSite/s or by sharing information either through an offline or online mode with KiRa9, you provide an express consent, that we may contact you via Email/SMS/Call to let you know about any new happenings, changes, newsletters, offers or to pass on any information that we may feel would be useful to you. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving any further communication, you can contact us at _______________ (insert email id) or call us at ____________ (insert phone number).

In case you are a Job-seeker and choose to share your resume on any of our Kira9 WebSite/s, it shall be deemed to be considered as an implied consent allowing us to share it with potential Job Recruiters. You give us express permission to share your personal information with Employers or Recruiters who have posted job opportunities that may be of interest to you on the Kira9 WebSite/s when you apply for those jobs.  
Polls and Surveys may be conducted by Kira9 or through any of our Kira9 WebSite/s. As a User, you may be invited to participate in polls and surveys. Whether or not you decide to participate in a poll or survey is completely up to you. After you complete a poll, you will be given access to the aggregate responses of the poll on a results page. Any data shared by you through such polls or surveys can be used by Kira9 for their internal purposes.

We may need to disclose certain personal information about you to companies and individuals we employ to perform functions on our behalf. However, no additional personal information pertaining to you, apart from the basic essential details shall be disclosed to any Third Party without acquiring your consent.

D] SECURITY & CONFIDENTIALITY  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties, your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Kira9 WebSite/s, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Kira9 network if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

  * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
  * enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations.
  * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
  * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Kira9 or any of our WebSite/s,our Users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners – like publishers, advertisers or connected sites for marketing, advertising, or other internal uses.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information on or through any of our Kira9 WebSite/s. We limit direct access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to perform their services and to offer a customized experience to all our User/s.

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to several self- regulatory frameworks. When Kira9 shall receive formal written complaints, we shall contact the User who made the complaint to solve the problem at the earliest. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our User/s directly.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the laws prevalent in India to protect personal information about you. We seek to ensure compliance with the requirements laid down under the Information Technology Act, 2000 and Rules made thereunder to ensure the protection and preservation of your privacy.

E] COOKIES  
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow), that enable the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use information collected from cookies to improve your experience and the overall quality of our services. We also use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third- party service providers to assist us in better understanding our WebSite/s visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

F] DISCLAIMER  
KiRa9 shall not be held liable for any exchange of personal information or data exchange that takes place between the User/s (whether Readers, Students, Contributors, Authors, Job Seekers, Recruiters or Advertisers) via the Kira9 WebSite/s online messenger service. KiRa9 shall not be held responsible for any communication that may take place between its User/s, outside the WebSite/s. KiRa9 and its Website/s serve merely as a platform for bringing together aspiring Students, Mentors, Business Schools, Universities, Job Seekers and Recruiters.

G] AGE RESTRICTION  
We at KiRa9 or any of our WebSite/s do not voluntarily grant access to users who are below the age of 18 years, nor do we voluntarily collect data from anyone under the age of 13 years. In case you notice any violation of this clause, then kindly contact us at _______________ (insert email id) or call us at ____________ (insert phone number) or on the address mentioned at the end of this Privacy Policy.

H] MOBILE PHONE ACCESS  
This Privacy Policy and all the terms and conditions mentioned herein shall be applicable even if any of the Kira9 WebSite/s are accessed by you through your Mobile Phones. Personal information or data shared with us through any of our Kira9 Mobile WebSite/s shall be managed in a way similar to our Website/s accessible via any computer platform. Any issues pertaining to internet data charges that may apply in such a case, shall be between you and your Mobile Internet Service Provider only. KiRa9 shall not be held responsible in any such event.

I] CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY  
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you here, by means of a notice on our  
home page or via an email, so that you may access and review the changes to this document in advance of your continued use of our WebSite/s. By continuing to use or access our WebSite/s after notice of changes has been sent to you or published on the Kira9 WebSite/s, you are consenting to the changes.

J] TERMS & CONDITIONS  
Please also visit our Terms of Use section which establishes the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of any of our Kira9 WebSite/s. You can access the same by clickinghere. (provide hyperlink)

In case of any queries regarding this Privacy Policy, contact us at the following address  
KiRa9 Edumedia Pvt Ltd  
310, Apeejay House, Bombay Samachar Marg, Fort, Mumbai, India. Email: ___________________  
Contact No.: 9321346317
